<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Pizza Recipes</string>
    <string name="homemade_title">Pizza with homemade sauce</string>
    <string name="homemade_description">Make pizza for the family with a homemade base and tomato sauce.
        The recipe is perfect to get kids involved in cooking. Top with mozzarella and fresh basil</string>
    <string name="homemade_method">Method
STEP 1
Tip the flour into a bowl, then stir in the yeast and 1 tsp salt.
        Make a well in the centre and pour in 200ml warm water (make sure it’s not too hot) along with the oil.
        Stir together with a wooden spoon until you have a soft, fairly wet dough.

STEP 2
Tip the dough out onto a lightly floured surface and knead for 5 mins until smooth.
        Cover with a tea towel and set aside for an hour or so or until the dough has puffed up and doubled in size.
        You can also leave the rough, unkneaded dough in the bowl,
        cover with a tea towel and leave in the fridge overnight and the dough will continue to prove on its own.

STEP 3
Meanwhile, make the tomato sauce. Put the oil in a small pan and fry the garlic briefly (don’t let it brown),
        then add the passata and simmer everything until the sauce thickens a little. Leave to cool.

STEP 4
Once the dough has risen, knead it quickly in the bowl to knock it back,
        then tip out onto a lightly floured surface and cut into two balls.
        Roll out each ball into a large teardrop that is very thin and about 25cm across
        (teardrop shapes fit baking sheets more easily than rounds).

STEP 5
Heat oven to 240C/220C fan/ gas 9 with a large baking sheet inside.
        Lift one of the bases onto another floured baking sheet.
        Smooth the sauce over the base with the back of a spoon, scatter over half the mozzarella,
        drizzle with olive oil and season. Put the pizza, still on its baking sheet,
        on top of the hot sheet in the oven and bake for 8-10 mins until crisp. </string>
    <string name="homemade_ingredients">Ingredients
300g strong white bread flour , plus extra for dusting
1 tsp instant yeast
1 tbsp olive oil
For the tomato sauce
1 tbsp olive oil , plus a drizzle
2 garlic cloves , crushed
200ml passata
For the topping
8 mozzarella pearls , halved
small bunch fresh basil</string>
    <string name="sourdough_title">Sourdough pizza</string>
    <string name="sourdough_description">Make homemade sourdough pizza with a wonderfully chewy crust.
        Try our margherita recipe, then customise with your favourite toppings</string>
    <string name="sourdough_ingredients">Ingredients
For the base
1 batch white sourdough (see step 1)
strong or plain flour , for dusting
For the topping
2 x 400g cans plum tomatoes
2 tbsp extra virgin olive oil , plus extra to serve
1 tsp dried oregano
300g mozzarella , torn into chunks
small bunch of basil , leaves picked (optional)</string>
    <string name="sourdough_method">Method
STEP 1
Make a batch of our white sourdough, following the recipe to the end of step 10.
        When the dough is ready, tip it onto a lightly floured surface and divide into six equal pieces.
        Roll into balls and leave to rest on a floured tray, covered with a damp teatowel,
        in the fridge for at least 4 hrs, and up to 18 hrs – the longer you leave the dough, the more sour it will taste.

STEP 2
Meanwhile, make the tomato sauce. Drain some of the juice from the plummed tomatoes
        and tip the rest into a bowl with the olive oil, oregano and a generous pinch of salt.
        Combine by either scrunching everything together with your fingers (this will make a chunky sauce)
        or blitz with a stick blender (this will make a smooth sauce). Chill until needed.

STEP 3
To make the pizzas, heat a grill to high and prepare an ovenproof frying pan.
        On a floured surface, push and stretch a ball of dough into a circle roughly the same size as the pan.
        Get the pan very hot, then working quickly and carefully, drape it into the pan,
        spread over some of the sauce, a handful of mozzarella and some basil, if using.

STEP 4
Cook for 2 mins, until little bubbles appear,
        then put the pan under the grill for another 2-4 mins until the sides are puffed up and the cheese has melted.
        Remove, drizzle with a little olive oil and cut into wedges. Repeat with the remaining dough.</string>
    <string name="no_yeast_title">No yeast pizza dough</string>
    <string name="no_yeast_description">Try this easy no yeast recipe for pizza dough using just flour, baking powder, salt and oil.</string>
    <string name="no_yeast_ingredients">Ingredients
350g plain flour
2 ¾ tsp baking powder
1 tsp salt
1 tbsp oil
additional toppings of your choice</string>
    <string name="no_yeast_method">Method
STEP 1
Heat the oven to 200C/180C fan/gas 6.

STEP 2
Mix together 350g flour, 2 ¾ tsp baking powder and 1 tsp salt in a small bowl, add 1 tbsp oil and 170ml water then stir until it forms a ball. If stiff, add more water, it should be soft but not sticky.

STEP 3
Knead on a floured surface for 3-4 mins. Roll into 2 balls, then flatten out.

STEP 4
Add toppings and bake each on a baking sheet for 15 mins.</string>
</resources>